Adam Sackfield

adam@adamsackfield.uk adamsackfield.uk github.com/adampaulsackfield 07713737666

Profile

My journey into the world of technology began as a personal interest, which soon became a passionate hobby. I was fascinated by technology and spent a great deal of my free time tinkering with gadgets and figuring out how things worked. I often found myself diving into problems, more for the journey than the end result. My first professional experience came when I joined the Genius Bar team at Apple. Here I was able to hone my skills in presenting solutions, objection handling, and diagnostic processes. I was inspired by the talented and innovative people I worked with, which motivated me to take my hobby to the next level. I enrolled in two bootcamps in Software Engineering and Cloud Engineering, which helped me to further develop my technical skills and fill in any gaps in my knowledge. Through my work on client projects with a team, I was able to explore new ideas and push the boundaries of what was possible within the given briefs.

Experience

TECHNICAL SPECIALIST, APPLE; MANCHESTER, UK - 2019-2023

- Diagnosing and resolving technical issues with Apple products, such as iPhones, iPads, and other devices.
- Maintaining accurate records of customer interactions and technical issues, and communicating effectively with other member of the Genius Bar team.
- Adhering to Apple's polices and procedures for customer service, privacy, and security.
- Provide expert technical support and exceptional customer service to ensure that customers receive the best possible experience with Apple products.

PERSONAL ASSISTANT, TRAVEL COUNSELLORS; MANCHESTER, UK - 2012-2019

- Assisting the travel counsellor with managing their schedule, booking appointments, and handling administrative tasks.
- Coordinating travel arrangements, including flights, accommodations, ground transportation, and other activities, to ensure that clients' needs are met.

 Maintaining accurate and up-to-date records of client interactions, travel arrangements, and financial transactions, and ensuring that client data is kept confidential and secure.

Education

DEVOPS CLOUD ENGINEERING BOOTCAMP, NOLOGY; REMOTE - 2022-2023

- Fast paced, intensive bootcamp focusing on DevOps Cloud Engineering.
- ▶ Built a collection of projects: Full-Stack, APIs, and DevOps CI/CD.
- Testing using Jest, Cypress, React Testing Library, and Junit.
- Notable tools: Packer, Ansible, and Terraform.

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING BOOTCAMP, NORTHCODERS; REMOTE – 2022-2022

- Industry-led curriculum, covering some of the top JavaScript frameworks.
- Taught best practices throughout, including version control, collaboration, TDD, and pair programming.
- Worked on solo projects as well as collaborative projects, using Agile Methodologies.

GCSES, CONEY GREEN HIGH SCHOOL; MANCHESTER, UK

Skills

- Strong understanding of JavaScript, Java, and Bash. With experience working with popular frameworks such as React, Express, and Spring Boot.
- Experience using SQL and NoSQL databased to model data and consume using APIs.
- Test Driven Development approach to development and following industry best practices.
- Proficient in DevOps tools such as Packer, Ansible, Jenkins, Vagrant, Docker, and Terraform used to orchestrate the deployment of multi-tiered applications.
- Experience working with various cloud providers such as AWS, GCP, and Digital Ocean.